Time synchronized by ProAce
Subtitle provided from barzy98
The Roble Sacred Kingdom, lying on a peninsula
to the southwest of the Re-Estize Kingdom.
Its territory is divided into northern
and southern halves by a great gulf.
The borders of the Sacred Kingdom are guarded by a massive wall
to protect against demihuman tribes in the bordering Abelion Hills.
An area also located near the Slain Theocracy.
It's a symbol of strength as well as the suffering
they face at the hands of their neighbors.
Orlando, it's time to change shifts.
Where's your report?
My apologies, Sergeant Baraja.
My thoughts were elsewhere.
But there are no changes to report today.
I wish I could see as clearly in the dark as you can.
I'd love to join you on the Night Watch someday, sir.
My sharp eyesight was earned through training, you know.
You can achieve the same thing if you work hard enough.
I'd argue that it takes talent to get results like that.
A talent your daughter inherited, it seems.
I'm so proud of her.
She is gifted, if I do say so myself.
Although it's unfortunate that she's so dead set on becoming a paladin.
I'm sure that she simply wants to follow in her
mother's footsteps, which I can hardly object to.
But she's no good when it comes to swordplay.
Her archery is excellent, however.
So if she needs a career role model, I sure wish she'd look to me.
Did you know she's still afraid of caterpillars?
What a silly little girl.
What is it?
Demihumans, there's no doubt.
Snakemen.
How many, sir?
It can't be a big deal.
Right?
They just keep piling up.
And it's not just snakemen, either.
This is bad news.
There's armats.
And ogres.
Are those caimans?
An invasion?
At this rate, we may need a national mobilization order.
I'll take your word for it, but I can't see much.
Have you spotted their leader yet?
I don't think so.
Surely a commander of a force that size would stick out.
Take positions, men.
And be prepared to fire.
I think you should return to your squad and wait for an update.
Good idea.
I'll get on that right now.
You be careful.
Should we shoot?
They're still too far, but it won't be too long, so listen close for my order.
I think I've spotted their leader.
Stop right there!
This is the territory of the Roble Sacred Kingdom!
Demi-humans like you aren't allowed to set foot here!
Disperse immediately!
Greetings, citizens of the Sacred Kingdom.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Jaldabaoth.
You mean the Great Demon Jaldabaoth?
You know of me.
How flattering.
I am indeed the one who orchestrated the grand feast
in Riesti's kingdom that was met with such rapturous applause.
However, if I must be given such a grandiose title,
I would prefer to be called Demon Emperor Jaldabaoth.
I have a feeling that's not just bravado.
Getting to the point.
I've come here to make your kingdom a living hell.
Wails, maledictions, and cries of pain will echo without end.
It will become a carnival of suffering.
You think we would ever allow such a thing?
This is not simply the Sacred Kingdom's first line of defense.
It is the only one that is required!
This wall guarantees the peace of every last person who dwells behind it!
It shall not be shaken, even before you!
Let's find out, shall we?
Now, allow me to offer you a gift in return.
Tenth-tier magic, Meteor Fall!
Take your sword and drive it through your throat!
Get here a bit faster next time.
I have no further critiques, so please begin the attack.
Come, demons.
Your job is to support the demihumans.
Also, find an appropriate way to drive the humans from the stronghold.
You may kill some of them, but don't get carried away.
We need a few to escape.
Good.
Everything is proceeding according to plan.
That said, I'm sure the outcome my lord orchestrates
will be far beyond even my wildest conjectures.
There is no greater joy than observing his genius in action,
and no greater lesson in how better to serve him.
What more could I ask for in this world?
The End Grandmaster Remedios!
If you turn right once more from this street,
you will reach the square where Jaldabaoth is waiting!
I see.
In that case, begin casting any long-lasting defense spells immediately.
Yes, ma'am!
Follow me!
Prepare yourselves, Jaldabaoth!
Take cover!
You'd better leave him to me!
Are you a paladin or a raging bull?
Perhaps my red tie provoked you.
Are you the one who calls himself the Demon Emperor?
Indeed.
And are you the princess who became sacred king?
Yes, I am none other.
Please, Princess Calca, there's no need to offer your name to this monster.
We've confirmed his identity and that's more than enough.
All that's left is to kill him.
Remedios, please, just give me a moment.
Sister, come on, show some patience.
Princess Calca's trying to gather information.
Tell me, what is your purpose in appearing before us alone?
If you want to conquer this country,
why did you leave your army behind this time?
I assume that you've heard of the
Adamantite-class adventurer, Momon of Darkness?
My plans for the Riesti's kingdom failed
due to the efforts of that powerful warrior alone.
If there is anyone in this kingdom with strength on his level,
then it's reasonable to assume that they would be guarding the sacred king.
Although it seems my concerns were without merit.
I had to check.
Those maids...
So this is the strongest paladin in the history of the Sacred Order?
How disappointing.
How dare you!
Try saying that again after I take off your head!
Control yourself!
You're just letting him provoke you!
Well, sacred princess, is there anything else you wanted to ask?
No, that is all.
The time's come.
Remember this, Remedios.
You are the sword that protects this land!
You are the justice that empowers the weak!
No matter what, we cannot allow further harm to come to our people!
Angel unit, forward!
Aaaah!
Flow Acceleration!
Holy Strike!
I see.
Casting Penetrate Magic, Holy Ray!
Casting Twin Penetrate Magic, Holy Ray!
The angels need to coordinate their attacks!
Stay focused!
That's good advice.
Even insects can be aggravating in a proper swarm.
Not enough!
You did it!
Not yet!
Destroy the building, but stay away!
Fireball!
You've proven yourself a nuisance.
It seems I'll have to put some effort into this battle.
Assuming you don't die from shock, that is.
Ready your angels!
All priests, attack at once!
Urgh!
Princess Calca!
Talar!
Maintain a safe distance!
You have to run away!
We can't defeat them!
At least not like this!
If they live, the kingdom lives.
That's enough.
Greater Teleportation!
Get away from her.
Princess Calca!
I don't sense the presence of any monsters.
Still, it may be safer to stay here a moment until the fog clears.
Would Dad wait?
Nehagaraha!
Uh, yes?
What in the world is happening here?
Can you explain this fog?
I'm afraid I can't, ma'am.
It defies all reason.
To start, there are no bodies of water nearby,
so there shouldn't be such thick fog around here.
Since we don't know the cause, we should watch and wait...
for now.
You're utterly useless.
Don't blame her, Grandmaster.
Squire Baraja has been a tremendous help.
We were able to avoid the demi-humans who
have overrun our kingdom thanks to her and her sharp eyes.
We owe our safe travels here to her.
That's not the point!
We can't afford to waste time, Gustav!
Every moment that we stall is another moment
that our people are being oppressed and killed!
What is that?
But...
we're on land.
It can't be!
Is this some sort of illusion, or what?
Oh...
No mistaking it, this is the sorcerer kingdom of Ainz Ul'Gone.
What a repulsive statue, to think that monster is their king.
Your feelings aside, please remember that
we're asking this kingdom for their help.
Momon of Darkness is the only one who can best Jaldabaoth.
If they won't lend his service to us, there's no hope.
We are at this undead's mercy.
I'm well aware of our situation, Gustav.
No humiliation is worse than failure.
I would do anything to save our home.
That includes bowing to a filthy undead, so don't you worry.
We are the paladin order, serving the sacred princess!
Chin up, and back straight!
Raise up our flag!
Welcome to the sorcerer kingdom of Ainz Ul'Gone.
My name is Riraba Yusvenya Ain Darun.
I'm a naga.
Our king is aware of your desperate situation and
is willing to grant you an audience right away.
However, there are some important details about this city
that you must be made aware of beforehand.
A dragon?
There's no panic.
You mean to tell me dragons are treated like citizens here too?
Indeed they are!
But that's nothing special in the least.
You'll find any number of races walking this kingdom's streets.
Including the undead.
Everything seems rather peaceful.
Representatives from the sacred kingdom, we welcome you all.
To begin, please allow me to introduce myself.
I'm the prime minister.
In other words, I'm overseer of the floor and territorial guardians here.
My name is Albedo.
Ah, I thank you for giving us such a cordial greeting.
From the sacred kingdom, my name is Remedios Custodio.
I'm the leader of the sacred paladin order.
We're truly honored your king has granted us an audience so quickly.
You have my deepest gratitude.
No need for thanks, I assure you.
His majesty has been terribly concerned.
The state of the sacred kingdom is quite troubling indeed.
I spoke to him about it personally.
Given the urgency of your kingdom's situation,
it's only natural that he would make time for you.
Yes, that's very charitable of him.
His majesty will now enter.
Everyone, bow your heads.
I present to you the great sorcerer king, Ainz Ul Gon.
You may now raise your heads.
I'm honored.
It must have been quite the journey for you,
coming from the far-off sacred kingdom.
And for your paladins as well.
An undead king, but he doesn't seem to hate humans.
Squire Baraja!
What were you thinking, speaking to the king like that?!
Grandmaster, please let her go!
I understand that Squire Baraja spoke without permission back there.
But think, she convinced the king to send Momon
to our country in two years instead of three.
So shouldn't she be praising her instead?
Do you know what you're saying?!
The entire negotiation could have fallen apart!
Listen, regardless of the result, we can't
praise someone for acting out like that!
I'm very sorry, Grandmaster.
And what exactly do you think that apology is worth?
What if they were offended and sent us away?
How would you take responsibility for that?
I'd pay with my life.
If this failed, we'd all be dead anyway.
So if the Sorcerer King didn't agree,
you might as well offer my head to apologize.
You think your measly life is worth that much?!
And you think I'd just agree to kill you?!
Though, you are tempting me.
Grandmaster, I believe you've made your point.
We couldn't have held out three whole years for Momon.
Nehoboraha.
You showed incredible resolve back there.
The Grandmaster may be harsh with you,
but she does recognize what you accomplished.
As for what's next, we'll try to renegotiate with the Sorcerer King soon.
The Grandmaster is anxious,
but this kind of negotiation often requires several meetings
to find a good outcome for both sides.
I understand your impatience.
It felt like our only hope was crumbling right before our eyes.
Still, the Grandmaster knows you only spoke up
out of concern for the Sacred Kingdom.
The thing is, she's carrying the entire weight
of our nation's future on her back right now.
You should be told the truth.
You don't know what happened when
the Sacred Princess faced Jaldabaoth.
I assume you've only heard what was reported
since you weren't at the battle in Kalinsha, correct?
Correct.
We were very particular about what was said.
As far as other countries know, the North was taken by
the Demi-Human Alliance, but the South is safe.
The Princess and her forces maintain high morale
despite their loss, and that's it.
Is that not true?
We must get Momon's help.
We can't leave here empty-handed.
Ready teleportation.
Get away from her!
You'll make a fine weapon.
Heheheheheheheheheheheheheheh!
K-K-Kill him!
No!
Let her go.
Stop it!
Let her go!
Enough!
What do I do now?
That's quite the heavy salary.
Huh?
This is Squire Baraja, please open the door.
Excuse me ma'am, the Sorcerer King is here to see you.
He wishes to speak in secrecy.
What?
Have you gone insane?
No need for any of that.
It's not the girl's fault.
If you have an issue, take it up with me.
Do pardon the sudden visit.
There are certain things I cannot speak of in public.
This requires a bit of discretion.
For example, there is a reason why I cannot
send Momon to help you right now.
It has not been long since the founding of my kingdom.
I am hardly a typical ruler, as none dead humans tend to fear me.
However, the presence of a reliable hero
like Momon puts their hearts at ease.
If he were to leave, I fear that my people might suffer.
That said, there may be a solution.
I have one demand.
If you can fulfill it, I would be willing to grant you
the services of someone equal in strength to Momon.
Do you mean that?
What is your demand, your majesty?
I fear we have little to offer right now.
I want maids.
Specific ones, that is.
I'm afraid you've lost me.
I recall seeing demon maids accompanying Jaldabaoth.
Is that who you're referring to?
Yes.
Before I continue, let me ask.
How much do you know about magic?
Next to nothing, I'd say.
I see.
Well, in simple terms, I suspect that Jaldabaoth is controlling
those maids with some sort of magical contract.
If he is defeated and the contract taken, I can command the maids.
They are known to be powerful servants.
I believe they would be a great boon to the Sorcerer Kingdom.
I understand.
Then we'll hand the maids over to you.
That said, I'm surprised there's someone
who compares to Momon in strength.
Can you tell me a bit more?
It's me.
Considering the nature of my request,
I don't think this should come as such a surprise.
And in case you have any concern,
I am even stronger than Momon.
Then I have no objections at all.
You sure?
I won't be bringing any help.
Also, I can teleport to any place that I've been before,
so I will come and go as I please.
I see.
Do you want an army as well?
Though I warn you, they will be undead.
There's no need.
As long as you truly possess enough power
to defeat Jaldabaoth, then I'll be satisfied.
We'll handle his forces ourselves.
When can you depart?
Tomorrow morning.
Excellent.
Wait, no!
Let's discuss this!
What in the world are you thinking?
The fact that he's undead aside, he's a king!
You'd have him fight Jaldabaoth to the death?
What do you suggest?
Accepting his undead army instead?
Our people would be terrified and our land tainted.
He's not just a sorcerer.
He's the ruler of a foreign nation.
What if he gets injured or even worse, killed?
Too bad.
King or not, he's a monster, right?
Whether he dies or the demon dies,
it's hardly any concern to us.
Wouldn't you say?
My point is, they're both enemies of mankind.
To be frank, if they wipe each other out,
that would be the best case scenario.
You mean that?
Does that embody the spirit of justice?
Of course!
Because it would save the lives of the innocent!
Squire Neia Baraja!
Yes, ma'am?
You will accompany the Sorcerer King.
Huh?
Stay by his side at all times and convince him
to be useful to us any way you can.
But don't provide too much intel about our home.
Sweet-talk him and make sure he stays happy.
Then we'll milk him for all he's worth.
What should I do?
I've never been the attendant of a king,
let alone an undead one.
Perhaps I should start up a conversation?
But if I displease him, I'm afraid he might kill me.
There's something on my face.
You seem to be glaring at it.
Huh?
No, please excuse my rudeness, your majesty!
No offense taken.
But are you uncomfortable riding with an undead?
Not at all, your majesty!
By the way, I wasn't glaring.
I inherited these fierce eyes from my father.
They are striking.
I do wish there was something we could talk about.
Ah, I know your visit was short.
But what did you think of my country?
It may have felt small in the eyes
of someone from the Sacred Kingdom.
It seemed like a wonderful place, peaceful and happy.
And it was the first time I've ever seen
so many different races living together.
Good, that's good.
Also, the statues of you were very impressive.
They certainly are big.
Ah, yes, that they are.
My subordinates insisted upon making them.
On top of that, we're planning to build more of them elsewhere.
That's so nice!
Then people outside of the capital
can witness your greatness too, right?
Ah, I see.
That's what my subordinates think too.
But I'm not certain that I agree.
I think it might be a bit short-sighted.
What do you mean by that?
The true greatness of a king cannot be shown in monuments.
It must be shown through their actions.
I want to be known for the peace and
prosperity created under my rule.
That is what I want people to see.
How wise.
You truly are a fine king.
By the way, how long will it take for us
to reach the Sacred Kingdom by carriage?
About ten days, I think.
A while, then.
In that case, I would like to learn more about you, Miss Baraja.
Perhaps you could begin by telling me why you decided to become a paladin.
I would be honored to tell you, though you may find it boring.
Do accept my most humble apologies, Your Majesty.
I know this is hardly a proper place to welcome
someone such as you, but please join us in the meeting room
so that we may discuss our plans.
Of course.
Since our situation has changed, let's determine
what our new course of action should be.
Before that, since I've agreed to help you,
I think I should know the full details
of what's happening in your kingdom.
Seeing as we're meeting in a cave,
things must be quite dire for your army.
It's clear that your north and south are separated geographically,
but I'm aware that a political divide exists as well.
Am I correct to assume that you will receive
no aid from the Southern Territory?
Also, Princess Calca's absence today can only mean one thing, I fear.
I can't believe you'd do so much at a mere glance.
Well then...
Sacred Princess Calca is missing, it's true.
Our High Priestess Kellard as well.
They faced Jaldabaoth, but we were separated
when the battle took a turn for the worse.
However, they use high-tier priestly magic,
so those two are far from helpless.
Although there's a good chance they've been captured,
I have faith that they're still alive.
Searching for them is a major priority, as is the liberation of our cities.
Our hope is to free our captured citizens and bolster our dwindling supplies.
Not far from here, there is a small city named Lloyds.
We've obtained information that people
of the royal family may be imprisoned there.
If that news is true, we need to rescue them right away.
This should be a simple task with a powerful
magic caster like Your Majesty on our side.
If you, or we, attack now, we'll make short order of the enemy.
You're worth ten thousand troops on your own.
I cannot meet your expectations.
You mean you won't fight?
Correct.
Or that is to say, I will only fight Jaldabaoth.
That is the only reason I have come after all.
He will be a formidable foe, so I must
conserve my magic if I hope to defeat him.
Oh, I see.
This is the Sacred Kingdom's war to wage.
I won't interfere with your affairs, but I won't follow your orders either.
If you want me to stand at the forefront of this operation, then I must lead.
In which case, you and your forces would be placed under my command.
Once that happened, I could negotiate with
the nobles of the Southern Territory and use
the best possible means to save this kingdom.
As far as we know, the Sacred Princess is still our ruler.
Regardless of the situation, we cannot fall
under the command of another kingdom.
Miss Baraja, your steps were unusually quiet.
Especially for someone trained to be a paladin.
My apologies.
My father was a ranger, so he taught me how
to use silent footwork when I was just a child.
If I recall correctly, you did mention that he was skilled with a bow.
Did he impart that knowledge to you as well?
I do have a bit of experience,
but that doesn't serve me since
paladins only fight with swords.
Those are the rules.
What a waste.
A paladin with a bow.
Interesting combinations open the path to rare job classes.
Yes, I like it.
Oh, um, thank you, your majesty.
Let me see.
How about I lend you this?
As I'm likely to cause you trouble during this endeavor,
you may consider it a token of my gratitude.
I can't accept such a fine gift from you!
And you don't owe a thing to a commoner like me!
Whether it was an order or not, you're taking care of me.
What station you have in life does not affect my appreciation of that.
Your majesty.
This is Ultimate Shooting Star Super.
I can't say I've ever seen a bow with such an elaborate name.
Sounds like a weapon that would appear in ancient myths.
Actually, you're not far off the mark.
This bow was made with rune technology,
an ancient and powerful art.
I want you to use it to protect me should the need arise.
I accept your gift.
And though I may be of humble skill,
I swear to protect you to the best of my ability, with loyalty.
Until you see this great endeavor to its end.
Onward!
How valiant.
Indeed.
Our paladins charge fearlessly into battle to protect the innocent.
And yet...
This is the end.
Thus begins our battle, to free this kingdom from Jaldabaoth's clutches!
For justice!
No!
Uh, by the way.
Are you not joining the battle, Miss Baraja?
The runes on that bow imbue it with great power.
I'm sure you would see outstanding results.
I couldn't.
I'm your majesty's attendant, right?
Y-yes.
Speaking of the bow, did any of the paladins happen to take notice of it?
Perhaps they asked to borrow it.
Always they had swords engraved with runes.
No, nothing of the sort.
That is to say, they took interest in it, of course.
But I assured them it wasn't something
they could ever hope to receive from you.
I see.
Yes, very well then.
Stand back.
Move away from the wall, humans.
This is bad.
I'll kill this child if you take another step!
And there's more where he came from, too!
That filthy coward.
Move back!
Do as he says!
And put down those weapons while you're at it!
Surrender without trouble and we will spare your lives!
Grandmaster Custodio.
This won't do.
If you teach the enemy that hostages are effective, they will continue using them.
Do you think I haven't realized that?
Please calm down.
We cannot lose focus.
Our goal is right there!
Shame on you!
You've lost your sense of justice so quickly!
I ask you, who did you pledge your sword to?
What would Princess Calca do right now?
She cares for all of her people.
She would never sacrifice the life of a child.
She'd find a better way!
Her justice!
Her wish!
Are you telling me that it's wrong?
If your raid ends in failure, all of this is meaningless.
We won't fail, and we won't bring dishonor to Princess Calca either!
We can find another way to win.
A way that will protect the innocent
rather than treating their lives like nothing!
No such method exists.
I've heard enough from you!
I'll negotiate with the enemy.
It won't work.
Squire, what did you just say?
It won't work, and more people will die.
You must sacrifice the one to save the many!
The Sorcerer King is correct.
It's the only choice we have!
There is no justice in that!
So what then?
We lose?
Is that just?
Please listen to Miss Baraja.
That's enough!
You've made your position clear.
I believe it's essential to take this city.
Arguing over justification will not serve that goal.
Very well.
I shall tip the scales myself.
You're sure about this?
Every victory requires some sacrifice,
but the cost will be less if I step forward in your stead.
Leave the Bafolk to me, and I believe
you will be satisfied with the results.
But people will be killed?
Unfortunately so, Grandmaster Custodio.
Humans!
This is your final warning!
Surrender, or die!
Why, imagine!
Fireball!
Your Majesty!
Forward, High Wraiths.
Move in and await my orders.
I'll go along with you.
Are you certain?
It's my duty.
Hmm.
In that case, you should wear this around your neck.
I don't know what it does, but thank you.
I will release an aura that instills fear in all those who come near me.
The necklace will protect you,
but tell the paladins that they must prepare
their own method to counteract the effects.
The priest should cast Lion's Heart.
I believe paladins can use Under Divine Flag.
Is that correct?
Yes, you're quite knowledgeable.
Miss Baraja, did you think I would use some sort of
unimaginable magic to save that young boy?
Y-yes.
I could have done so if it was the correct course of action.
However, if we teach the enemy that hostages are effective,
they will continue to use prisoners inside the City of Shields.
Then, the paladins' hesitation will cause further harm.
But I have demonstrated that hostages are of no use.
It seems cruel, but it will prevent further sacrifices.
Your judgment is correct, Your Majesty.
Please, let me!
No.
This was my decision.
Bafolk will pay for this.
I am the ruler of the Sorcerer Kingdom, not the ruler of this country.
If that boy was a citizen of my kingdom,
then it would have been my responsibility to protect his life.
Of course.
Your Majesty, you're like justice itself.
Hm?
I fear I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
I mean, your reasoning is right, and I believe that your actions are just.
There is no justice or injustice in my actions.
I only wish for the peaceful lives of myself and my children.
There is nothing more.
That is everything.
Nolan...
I am the one who killed this child.
A monster!
You did this?
Yes.
To save all of your lives.
To save us?
It seems you have something to say.
Then let me ask you this first.
Why did you fail to protect your own child?
I tried, of course.
But he was taken away from me.
Then why are you still alive?
A person's value is in the eye of the beholder.
But there is no one in the world who you should value more than your own child.
So I ask, why didn't you give up your life to protect him?
Why are you alive when he is dead?
This was your failure.
You have no right to blame others.
You can say that only because you're strong.
That's right.
It was my strength that saved you, and my strength that killed your son.
If you say that you're weak, then it is
no surprise that everything is taken from you.
So that means you can just do whatever you want?
It does.
If I am strong, then who will stop me?
What I say will become right.
That is the way of this world!
I will forgive your Albus because I take pity on you.
I'll leave you with your child.
You should mourn him.
If I were weak, everything would be taken from me as well.
That is why I desire strength.
Boundless strength.
Your Majesty.
It seems the enemy leader is up ahead.
Will you come with me?
Of course!
Are they dead?
This is the work of my raids.
I sent them ahead of us to scatter fear amongst our foes.
Is that him?
Interesting.
He has a number of magic items.
I wonder which one counted the raids.
My name is Buser.
They call me the Grand King!
He's a king?
That can't be good.
Your army is defeated.
Do you wish to die, or do you wish to submit to me?
I shall allow you to choose.
Bow my head to you?
I am still a king!
Bowing to that demon was enough!
Fine then.
I'll play with you a bit.
By the way, goat, I see you're
armed to the teeth with magic items.
But strangely, I don't sense any power
from those skulls dangling at your waist.
What?
You haven't heard of fashion?
They're just bones!
Very well, to each his own.
Now let us begin.
Create greater item!
All appraisal magic item.
He defeated that terrifying demi-human in a split second!
I knew the Sorcerer King was amazing, but this is unreal!
This is it.
I sense an overwhelming presence of fear in death.
They're orcs!
You're an undead.
What do you want?
Nothing.
I have simply come to set you free.
Wait, your majesty!
They're demi-humans, aren't they?
So these orcs must be minions of Jaldabaoth!
Really, Miss Boraha?
Surely you don't believe that.
Take a closer look.
We have not attacked any human country, I can assure you.
What's your name?
I am Dyel of the Gan Zu tribe.
Servant to no one.
If you are not at war like the rest of the demi-humans,
is that why you were imprisoned here?
Not all of the demi-human tribes in the Abelion Hills
submitted to the demon willingly.
Many were forced into submission, you could say.
We orcs resisted to the end,
as punishment Jaldabaoth brought us to this wretched place.
What does that mean?
What did he do?
Honestly, dare I even imagine?
It would seem I asked an insensitive question.
I will not demand that you join my army.
I will free you to go where you please.
But do you have somewhere in mind?
We'll find the rest of our tribe, then go someplace that Jaldabaoth can't reach.
In that case, you should come to my kingdom.
We refuse!
Undead are the enemy of all living things.
We wouldn't be safe.
No, I assure you, there's nothing terrifying about my country.
He's telling the truth!
He may be undead, but he is kind to the living and protects all his subjects.
He loves his children and treats demi-humans equally.
He's truly... Miss Baraja, that's enough!
But your majesty!
You may not believe us, but I swear on my honor
as Arinsul Gond that you would never be treated like this under my rule.
My subjects are my treasures.
They must not be harmed.
However, I will not force you to submit to me.
I can teleport you to your village, if that's what you want.
We're strangers.
Why are you being so generous?
I will defeat Jaldabaoth.
To do so, I must weaken him.
Spreading word of my kindness will undermine his influence.
If he rules over others with fear, as you said,
there may be demi-humans who wish to betray him.
I understand.
Then I wish you luck.
Miss Baraja, stand outside for a moment, please.
All right.
To his majesty, humans and demi-humans are both worth protecting equally.
This is the meaning of true kindness.
Pardon the wait.
Your majesty, so this is where you've been.
Has something happened?
Don't worry.
Good news this time.
We found Sacred Princess Calca's elder brother, here in the city.
Prince Caspond, this is the man who
has been aiding our kingdom and liberated the city.
He is known as the Sorcerer King, Ainz Ul Gon.
It is truly a pleasure to meet you.
Welcome, Sorcerer King.
It's a pleasure to meet you as well, Prince Caspond.
I'm glad you're safe.
I apologize for meeting you in such a terrible state.
A noble's elegance isn't a matter of appearance.
Thanks to your generous aid, I was set free from those demons.
I would like to sincerely thank you for the charity
that you have shown to me and my people.
I trust that the Sorcerer King is gone for the night.
Yes, we have prepared a room for him.
He doesn't know that we're meeting.
Good then.
Let us discuss our future.
First of all, the Sacred Princess.
I hear that my little sister Calca is currently missing.
Have the demi-humans taken her?
We have suggested such a possibility
to the Sorcerer King, but she is most likely dead.
We have seen no evidence of that yet.
Even if that's the case, we should be able
to resurrect her as long as we can find her body.
My sister Kellert is alive out there somewhere, and I know she could do it.
We should continue searching for her as well.
I agree that recovering Calca should be a priority.
So, to that end, I will make this city our base.
From here, we'll wage war against Jaldabaoth's army.
That's far too reckless.
We may have high walls, but if the enemy surrounds us,
it'll be over when we run out of food.
You don't plan to go to the Southern Territory?
I'll send a messenger instead.
In truth, those nobles won't help us much.
They all want the Sacred Seat, which means
they're hoping for news of my sister's death.
Regardless of our circumstances, I cannot beg people like that for help.
And as for the Sorcerer King, he's here to fight Jaldabaoth.
Once he acquires his demon maids, he will leave the kingdom, correct?
But that would create a problem for us.
Even if their leader is killed, there are plenty of
demi-humans we need His Majesty to call.
I know, sir, but that's not the arrangement we agreed upon, unfortunately.
It would be easy for him to thin their numbers with his magic.
And the more demi-humans he kills, the less our innocent citizens die.
Tell me, which would you rather choose?
An agreement that you made with an undead,
or the lives of our kingdom's people?
The lives of our citizens, obviously!
I'm so happy you see it my way.
We know what he's capable of, so let's see if
we can put the Sorcerer King to work.
Enemy attack!
Quite the force they've brought.
We have about 10,000 soldiers.
The enemy must have four times that.
Our only hope for victory will be surviving
till assistance comes from the south,
unless we can make the enemy retreat.
Grand Master, so this is where you've been.
Oh, it's you.
Excellent timing, Gustav.
I'd like to get your take on this, too.
I'd love to discuss my ideas, assuming I could come up with any.
But there's a small complication we need to deal with first.
What is it?
The citizens are troubled.
They're worried about the upcoming battle,
and they keep asking if the Sorcerer King will be lending his aid.
You know what he told us.
If he doesn't conserve his magic power,
he won't be able to defeat Jaldabaoth.
That's the deal.
So until the Demon Lord shows up, he won't lift a finger.
The issue is that many people saw him when he recaptured the city.
They know he has abilities that far exceed the Paladin's,
so they're looking to him for protection.
If the citizens find out that their hero won't be standing with us,
I fear that their morale will plummet.
He's their hero?
You're talking about an undead!
That doesn't matter to them!
And besides, better they think of him as a hero than a ruler.
What if they want him as Sacred King?
We still have a Sacred Princess, okay?
She can't be dead.
The enemy must be holding her hostage somewhere to keep an upper hand.
Yes, my apologies.
But it is a real concern.
I fear the seat of the Sacred Princess may be at risk.
Princess Calca is a beloved ruler!
Do you think his concerns are valid?
Well, since we're Paladins, of course we don't
consider the Sorcerer King to be a hero.
But I do get the impression around town that
the citizens are starting to think of him that way.
He exhibited so much power, I can hardly blame them.
Just what are you saying?
Do you think it was a mistake to bring the Sorcerer King here, Gustav?
No, I wouldn't say that.
It was the best decision you could have made at the time.
All right.
Then what would you do now?
Although the odds are not in our favor,
we must drive off the enemy on our own.
If we don't, the fighting may not end even if Jaldabaoth dies.
We must protect our own kingdom.
Still, we wait.
We've been sitting here for three days.
I heard that city was held by Grand King Buser.
Is that the issue?
Are you afraid of the enemy who killed him?
They must be quite formidable indeed.
Sir Vijar, no need for you to get so worked up.
You're such a child.
Why not learn a bit of patience before you mouth off?
If we wait much longer, you'll die of old age.
That's enough from the both of you.
We can't have any dissent in our ranks.
I would have to report the matter to Lord Jaldabaoth if we did.
As for the reason why we haven't attacked yet...
Lord Jaldabaoth ordered us to move our forces into place,
but to pause a few days so that the humans could watch us.
He wanted their fear to fester and grow.
I can't complain.
That's quite clever.
Now keep in mind, he didn't designate an exact amount of time.
So I say we attack the day after tomorrow.
There was one additional order.
He said it's very important.
We need to leave a few humans alive and allow them to escape from the city.
Very well.
And that means we can massacre the rest of them, yes?
If you so please.
Now, spend the next two days replenishing your strength.
Squire Neah Baraja here.
You may enter.
Your Majesty, I've been informed I'm to be deployed
to the front lines as a member of the Sacred Paladin Order.
Therefore, I will be unable to continue my duty as your attendant.
I wanted to offer an apology before I set off.
I have used my magic several times already.
Jaldabaoth may be aiming to whittle it away with his forces.
If he does not appear in this battle, do not expect me to come to your aid.
Yes, I understand.
Even so, it is my duty as part of this kingdom
to protect as many innocent people as I possibly can.
Those in pain and those who cannot
protect themselves must be cared for.
I like that look in your eyes.
And so, Squire Baraja, I will lend you a few items.
What?
No, wait!
You've already lent me this bow!
I wondered if it was even appropriate for me to use it in this battle.
I only accepted it so I could better serve you.
This is the armor of the demihuman king I defeated a few days ago.
I'm certain it will keep you safe.
And this is known as a visor mirror shade.
It helps to keep your vision clear, but it's also— Your Majesty!
I appreciate it, but I can't possibly borrow all these!
Then why not?
How about a promise in exchange?
When they're no longer needed, you must come and return them to me.
Thank you very much.
I hope I... I mean, I'll definitely survive and return these.
It's over!
There's no way we can win against that!
If the Sorcerer King came and thinned their numbers, maybe we could...
His Majesty isn't coming.
He will not be taking part in this battle.
Wait, aren't you the Sorcerer King's attendant?
Or, I mean, you were, at least.
Yes, that's me.
Then do you know why he won't help us?
His majesty needs to conserve his magic power
for the fight against Jaldabaoth.
He's the only one who can kill that demon.
That's all.
So we must make do on our own today.
We're outnumbered.
He'll tear right through us.
Are you ordering us to die?
What do you mean?
This is our kingdom to protect.
In the end, this is on our shoulders.
It's our duty.
And the Sorcerer King?
He's not even from this place.
He's been generous enough.
We can't use our weakness as an excuse to rely on him.
It's our kingdom and our war.
It's our people that we must protect.
So I'll fight because that is justice.
The demi-humans are strong.
We're not even knights.
We don't stand a chance.
But that doesn't change the fact that
someone has to protect my wife and child.
Huh?
So I'll fight.
I have to.
Good.
And I'll fight with you.
Don't be afraid.
Under divine flag!
The enemy's arrows won't rain down forever.
Stay strong!
Even with this, they're still too far away.
It's coming!
Pull back!
Hurry!
We have to fight!
If you have a bow, then shoot!
And if you don't, then throw rocks!
We just aren't strong enough.
I know it hurts, but we don't have
the power to save those children!
Ugh!
Stop holding back!
Attack them while you still can!
We can't protect those children!
She's right!
I know you.
If they get past those walls, the women and children here
will suffer a fate worse than death!
You have to do it for your families!
We've got no choice!
Attack!
Bring more stones!
Oh, no!
I'm okay.
This must be his power!
Tell the priest we need support, Magic!
Stab them with your spears while they're climbing up!
Ready shields!
First line, drop them!
Let's go!
Second line, into position!
Third line, spears forward!
Fourth line, it's your turn!
Spears forward now!
Paladins, protect against fear before we face the enemy!
Under divine flag!
This is it.
All forces ready.
Open the gates!
You're not worth the dirt you stand on!
Your insect-ridden hides are so filthy,
they're not even suited to wipe my ass!
Spears, pull!
Spears, stab!
Now, firebomb!
I can't fight three of their generals at the same time.
Paladin Sabicus!
Paladin Esteban!
Yes, ma'am!
They're strong.
I need you to hold two of them back for now.
In the meantime, I'll kill the third one.
Leave it to us!
I'll fight to my last breath!
I'm fine facing all of you at once, if you prefer.
Do you think I would deny myself the pleasure of sending you to hell?
Not on my life!
Ha ha ha ha!
She's a fight you own just like you, sir Vijar.
We'll let her give you that fight you're so hungry for.
Impressive, human.
That's a fine sword you've got.
Tell me your name before you die.
I'm Remedios Custodio.
Well, how fortunate!
You're hailed as the strongest paladin in the whole kingdom, aren't you?
Ha ha ha ha!
All that I seek is glory.
I'm Vijar Rajandala.
I'll take your head, human.
After doing so, I will inherit the title of Demon Claw at long last!
That's enough out of you!
Strong strike!
Fortress!
Power claw!
Strong strike again!
Ha ha ha ha!
Mine's already dead.
Oh no.
Mine didn't put up much of a fight.
Who's the slow one now, boy?
Shall I lend a hand?
I'm here for glory.
Why would I want help?
It would seem we're free to do as we please, Madam Nasrene.
Perhaps we should break through that line of shields
and head further into the city.
Like hell you will!
Not so fast!
How dare you take a back on our duel!
Hold shield!
Maintain your position!
I only get one of these, but here goes!
Extreme holy strike!
Ahhhhh!
What the hell?
Why didn't it work?
That certainly looked impressive, but it hardly stung at all.
Was it just to frighten me?
My holy light strikes down evil without fail.
After all that suffering you put us through,
after starting this damned war, you're still not evil?!
If it's any consolation, it did look nice.
Why, it nearly blinded me.
Fine work, human.
Now they'll tell tales of how I survived your greatest attack without flinching.
Since you've played your part so well, if you surrender, I'll kill you quickly.
You have your fun, sir Vijar, but we can't all afford to waste our time on one woman,
so we're going to continue conquering the city without you.
You protect the militia, I'll fight alone.
These are my people, and I have swore to keep them safe.
Pay her no mind, Madame Nasrene.
I believe you have just the spell to clean up those weaklings behind her.
Indeed I do.
Showdown declaration!
I can't move.
As long as you fight me, you'll be fine.
You will give me my due.
Fireball!
Wall of Skeleton!
I believe there's a lesson to be learned here.
But three generals against one just isn't very sporting.
Who is that, an undead?
So it would appear.
My, I believe that's an elder lich.
The Sorcerer King!
He'll save us!
Your Majesty, please!
We're going to die!
What do you think you're doing here?
I believe that should be rather obvious.
I came to save your lives.
Is that so?
Then I'll leave this to you.
The Sorcerer King will handle the front line!
We will act as reinforcements for whoever needs assistance.
All soldiers, follow after me!
Never in my life have I been treated with such blatant disrespect.
I thought it would be useful to have the Grandmaster of the Paladins
owe me a favor, but she's so rude!
She doesn't appreciate me at all!
Why would an undead come to the rescue of humans?
Are you being controlled by a necromancer, perhaps?
That woman doesn't hold you in very high regard, does she?
She left you here to die!
Silence!
What did you do?
I demanded silence, if I recall.
What did he...
I miscalculated.
Kill the demihumans!
If I'd known it would turn out this way,
I would have focused my efforts on Miss Baraja instead.
Heed my words, for I am Jajan, and I am taking their commander's head!
Naya Baraja has slain Jajan of the Lagon!
Be careful when approaching that human girl.
She's wearing the Grand King's armor!
So was she the one who killed Buser?
Her eyes have a wicked glare!
Looks like she's hungry for blood!
And that bow is brimming with power!
The Mad-Eye Archer!
Who is she?
Miss Baraja, this area is done for.
Please escape.
I can't do that!
I have to return this weapon.
But if I'm seen fleeing after receiving such a powerful gift,
it will reflect poorly on His Majesty.
I must stand firm.
Like hell I'd run!
I'm scared.
She's faltering!
Finish her off!
Attack from all sides!
This is it...
I'm dead...
Dad...
Mom...
Your Majesty...
Mine.
That was a close one.
Your...
Majesty?
Miss Baraja, rest and let me help you.
You shouldn't move.
Why is it so quiet?
No, that's a waste, Your Majesty.
I'll be...
fine.
No, no.
I'll give you something to recover your fatigue as well.
Forgive me for not reaching you sooner.
Your Majesty, I'm worried about you.
What about fighting Jaldabaoth?
What if he attacks and your magic is spent?
You could die.
I will face that when the time comes.
In this case, I had no choice.
I had to save you.
I see now.
I'm finally sure.
About what?
About what justice means.
I had it right before.
It really was you, just like I thought.
I'm afraid you might be a bit delirious.
Justice takes strength and courage.
Because if you're too weak, you can't uphold it.
But that doesn't mean that might alone makes right.
It's what you do with that strength that makes it just.
Like helping others.
Using your power to protect the weak, even when it might bring harm to yourself.
Like you did.
That's why I say you are justice itself.
Your Majesty!
We're all so grateful.
Even though we're not your subjects, you came here and saved our lives.
It was a mere trifle.
But I do have a favor to ask.
If you would like to express your gratitude, take her to a safe place until the battle is won.
Thank you.
Neia Baraja and everyone else in this kingdom, you may leave the rest to me.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
You're our hero!
Hooray for the Sorcerer King!
Hmph.
Incredible.
That's 40,000 demihumans wiped out.
This is a victory for the history books, my lord.
Don't you think?
It is a victory, but I would not call it ours to claim.
The Sorcerer King claimed the glory today, and he did it alone.
You're wrong!
All of us fought hard to save this city.
Some lost their lives.
That they did, and you were there on the front line.
You saw it firsthand.
Our paladins and our citizens fought and died for this land.
No victory would be possible without them.
That much I can accept.
But frankly, despite their efforts, we would have lost without the Sorcerer King's aid.
Am I wrong?
Let me remind you, he only joined us in the middle of the fight!
Think about all of the brave people who died before then!
Our citizens, our paladins, our priests!
You're saying they sacrificed everything for no reason?!
Grandmaster...
You saw what he was doing!
He was showing off just to get people on his side!
This war is nothing but a game to him, I swear.
Wait, that's it.
Jaldabaoth and the Sorcerer King must be working together.
Look at what happened.
He's the only one who really benefited from this fight.
It all makes sense now!
He weakens our kingdom, but still plays the hero.
Then in the end, he'll conquer us!
I'm sure of it!
Grandmaster Custodio, this has clearly taken a toll on you.
Go and rest for now.
I can't!
This is an order.
Get inside!
Hurry!
Jaldabaoth, come for us!
Forgive me if I'm interrupting your victory celebration,
but I'm afraid the battle's not over yet.
Steal the sword!
Princess...
Calca...
My goodness, I suppose she wasn't a
good weapon after all, falling apart like that.
Still, she would have remained in one piece at least
if you hadn't rushed in swinging your sword like some kind of savage.
What a beautiful scream!
Now then, you must be the Great Sorcerer King.
Anzalgar, was it?
Or should I call you Your Majesty instead?
Do pardon me.
I'm a demon, but that's no excuse to be rude.
Let's dispense with the formalities.
I assume you've come here to kill me,
so manners are hardly my priority at present.
Yes, I want you dead.
We could butcher each other's forces all day,
but this won't be settled till the two of us meet in battle.
But I know you're strong.
Stronger even than Momon.
Which is why I've constructed a plan
to ensure my victory beyond all doubt.
The demon maids are here too?
Well, well.
Your Majesty, do as you must.
Don't worry about us.
Consider it, you little human.
Don't worry, you'll get your slow and painful deaths once I kill your savior.
Say your goodbyes.
We shall wait for you at the Clock Tower in the center of the city.
I'm looking forward to this, Sorcerer King!
Prince Kasbond, I will buy you some time.
You should order any people near the center of the city to evacuate immediately.
I understand.
But wait!
You've already used so much magic to help us and you haven't rested at all!
Are you going to be able to win?
It certainly will be dangerous, but I fear I have no choice in the matter.
What do you mean?
The people of the Sorcerer Kingdom need you.
What if you die out there?
I made a promise as a king.
I must keep it.
Even if the circumstances aren't as I planned,
the demon has come to me and so I will destroy him.
Then the maids will be mine!
Message.
Ponzo, have you noticed anyone in the area?
Pleiades?
Oh yes, I know they're here.
No signs of any players or world items this time either, huh?
Was what happened to Shalltear just a fluke or what?
Never hurts to be extra careful.
I'll figure it out someday.
Everything else is set.
Now all I have to do is follow Demiurge's plan, so it should be easy.
Even if I screw something up, I'll just say I did it to test him.
This wouldn't be an issue if Demiurge didn't somehow
get the impression that I was a genius.
Half the instructions he gave me for this plan were just,
go with the flow, I trust your judgment.
He and Albedo, keep hitting me with these completely insane ideas.
Whoever heard of a king going alone to aid another country?
I'm out of my depth here!
Think about these things for a sec!
Okay, you got this, dude.
Everything's fine.
Just clear this and it's smooth sailing.
This is just a plain old evil lord of wrath.
Level 84.
Only difference is that Demiurge summoned this one.
Despite the fire, it's a pure warrior-type monster,
so that means powerful physical attacks and high HP.
I assume you've been informed of the plan?
Yes, of course, my lord.
Ready whenever you are.
All right.
Just to clarify, after the battle is won, you're going
to summon your demon to attack the city?
That is correct, my lord.
In that case, I have two requests.
First, I'd like some support on a personal project
that hasn't been going well.
Nothing too fancy.
And secondly, I cannot let my combat skills grow dull,
so I want you to order your summoned demon to fight me seriously.
But, my lord...
We understand.
Albedo!
However, the evil lord of wrath will probably not be
enough to satisfy someone of your prowess.
Why don't we have the demon maids join the battle as well?
Maximize magic!
Reality!
She's doing it too?
I fear I may accidentally kill the ladies.
Then we'll use greater doppelgangers to fight you in their stead.
Their performance won't disappoint, I assure you.
Hm?
Why am I so weak?
No, I said it myself.
Power isn't enough.
Even if I was as strong as a demon lord, it wouldn't matter.
But his majesty is different.
He's the only one who embodies justice.
Please, your majesty!
You must triumph!
You must!
Your sorcerer kin is dead by my hand!
You lied!
And I owe it all to you selfish humans.
If the sorcerer king had been in proper form,
this victory surely would have eluded me.
But he used his magic power to help you worms again and again.
He was a fool of a king undone by his own misguided sense of kindness.
But as you can see, he's dealt me terrible blows, so I must depart and rest.
I will spare your lives for now, but I will return in time to strike you down.
Until then, let your despair grow thick.
I don't believe you!
You're nothing but a damn liar!
You think I trust the words of a demon?
Demon!
That bow of yours is truly a fine weapon.
It has been ages since I've seen such workmanship.
Why, you could have finished me off.
A true demon slayer, that.
Tell me more of this bow.
What is it made from?
Go to hell!
Hold on.
Could it have been made with rune technology
thought to have been long lost?
Enough!
I won't say another word to you!
Well, seems that's the best I can do.
Time for greater teleportation.
You foul worm!
Your Majesty.
Three days.
It's already been three days since the disappearance of
His Majesty, and this is all I can accomplish.
We need to form a search unit and find him as soon as possible.
We're wasting time when there's none to spare.
Why won't Prince Kaspan do anything to help?
No, it's my fault for not being strong enough.
If I had the power, I could go search for him myself.
If justice takes strength, then weakness must be evil.
Squire Neha Baraja!
Prince Kaspan has requested your presence.
All right, I'll see him now.
We can practice later, sorry.
No problem.
I don't think we'll be catching up with you yet, but I do appreciate the lessons.
We have to practice while we can for when the demi-humans come back, right?
That's right.
We'll continue our training and grow stronger every single day.
Weakness is a sin, so never give up.
In regards to the Sorcerer King, well...
You've decided to send a search and rescue team?
As I've told you many times before, that's not possible.
We think the Sorcerer King must have landed in the Abileon Hills when he fell.
It's full of demi-humans.
Completely unsafe.
Unless we prepared a sizable force, we would just be
sending soldiers there to die senseless deaths.
That aside, we should at least search near the city in case he fell there.
There's no point.
You saw it yourself.
No one can survive a fall like that.
The Sorcerer King's dead and gone.
His Majesty is still alive!
Squire, stop!
You're the only one holding onto this ridiculous idea!
If you two are done, I still have something else to say.
But before I start, we have a rather unusual
new ally that I need to introduce to you.
I'll call her in now.
Do not be alarmed.
This is Emissary Bebebe.
A Zern?
Yes, that's correct.
Her people are currently trying to rebel against Jaldabaoth.
They've only been following his orders because a member
of their royal family has been taken hostage.
We cooperated to ensure our king's safety,
but when we left the hills, the demons killed him anyway.
Which means the prince is our only remaining male.
He's currently locked away in a tower in
a city about five days southwest of here.
They want us to aid them in a rescue operation.
The Zern prince is being held in Kalinsha.
It is an essential city in our northern territory.
So we'll form a small alliance, rescue the Zern prince,
then liberate Kalinsha together.
If you grant us your cooperation, we have
3,000 soldiers who can help you take back the city.
And after that, we should be able to send out
a rescue unit to search for the Sorcerer King.
It's too dangerous to search the Abelion Hills on our own,
but we can do it with the help of the Zerns.
What I'm getting at, Squire, is that I want you on the job.
Infiltrate the city and rescue the prince.
So who will be joining me on this mission?
Well, that is another surprise.
After the Sorcerer King fought with Jaldabaoth,
one of the demon mates came to the city and surrendered to us.
But why?
Although the Sorcerer King did not triumph in battle,
it seems that he was able to seize control of one of the maids.
She is now loyal to him instead.
Neia Baraja here to see you.
Could you please show yourself?
Hi.
Wow, what a great face.
So you're Jaldabaoth's maid they're holding you here?
Uh-huh.
Though to be more accurate, I'd say I'm actually Lord Ainz's maid now.
You mean his majesty, right?
Anyway, what do you want with me?
We need to talk.
I was hoping that you could help me with the mission.
Here, drink.
What is that?
It's a chocolate drink.
A bit high in calories though, like 2,000.
But I wouldn't worry about it.
Getting fat from eating delicious things isn't bad.
In fact, one of the Supreme Beings even said you could call it a life goal.
Well, guess I'll give it a try.
So sweet.
Want another one?
May I?
It's really delicious.
Thank you so much.
Never mind that.
I need to ask you some questions, all right?
Hm?
Well, first, I know you're a demon maid, but no one told me your name.
Maybe you heard, but I'm Neia.
I was serving as an attendant for his majesty, the Sorcerer King.
I know, yeah.
I was warned about your scary-looking eyes.
You can call me Shizu.
What's the mission?
All right, I understand.
The two of us will sneak into the castle and save the prince from that tower.
When we're done, your army and the Zerns will take back Kalinsha.
Correct.
Also, the Zerns gave me a warning.
They said there may be a great demon at the castle.
We might run into it on the way to the prince's room.
Do you know anything about it?
There are three, but lucky for us, they take turns watching the city,
so there shouldn't be more than one around.
That's good, but how strong are these things?
Well, all right, then how strong are they compared to you?
Hard to say.
I know they're weaker than Lord Ainz.
Call him His Majesty.
His Majesty the Sorcerer King.
I think that Lord Ainz is a little too casual, especially coming from a maid.
Just what do you mean?
He told me I should call him that himself.
I think it's just fine.
He gave me specific permission to use his name, so it's Lord Ainz.
Understand me?
Hold on!
But you just met him.
You're saying he's told you to do that during the fight?
I'm afraid you have to face the truth.
I'm sorry.
I know this has come as a great shock to you, but I'm special.
It's all right.
Not everyone can start out at the top.
Someday, if you work hard and you keep the faith,
I truly believe that you can be part of the Lord Ainz Club with me.
You have potential.
Shizu...
It's an expert's job to guide a trainee.
I think that we'll make a good team.
Well, thank you.
That's good at least.
I know that I just met you, but anyone who's able
to appreciate the greatness of Lord Ainz should be given mercy.
Even though you're a demon and even though
you're a little bit confusing, I have to agree.
Our mutual love of His Majesty will see us through.
I'm glad that I met you.
You're a human, but those bold eyes are very good.
I admit when you first came here, I thought it wouldn't matter
if you died on the mission, but now I will protect you.
Uh...
Lord Ainz gave me one order before the end of the battle.
He told me to cooperate with you and your allies.
No dying, but I'll do anything else to help you out.
Works for me.
Good.
What did you just do?
What is this weird thing?
I put these on cute things, or on you in this case.
Okay, but what is it and why is it on my head?
I know.
You're like a little sister.
Huh?
Okay, fine.
Now take it, but stick it someplace you can see.
Okay.
Are we done talking?
No, wait, one more thing.
Once we've rescued the prince, I want to search for His Majesty.
I mean we still need to find out where His Majesty fell down.
Sounds good to me.
Yes, let's do that.
Really?
Thing is, we don't know if His Majesty is all right or not yet.
He might be stuck in enemy territory.
I have faith that he'll pull through somehow, but I fear the worst.
What are you talking about?
He's fine.
He's not dead.
The fact that Lord Ainz has me under his control is proof.
Why are you crying?
I'm happy that he's still alive.
Wow, it's a whole snot bridge.
I'm kind of impressed.
I'll wash it and give it back, okay?
Really, I'm so sorry.
This is embarrassing.
Kalinsha is just up ahead.
Stop there.
We're just bringing in rations.
Are you satisfied yet?
That was rough.
You've got some meat in your hair.
Hmm?
Need a towel?
I'm never hiding in a barrel of raw meat again.
Well, I mean, we'll have to do it when we sneak out.
That's so handy.
Are you ready?
Ready.
The Zarin Prince is being held captive in a detached castle tower.
We can only reach it by crossing the Sky Bridge,
which is connected to the building we're in now.
Unfortunately, before we can make it to the bridge,
we'll have to get through a long passageway that has no places to hide.
Understood.
And after that?
We'll enter a room where some rope has been prepared.
Then we'll rappel down to another floor.
Thanks, Shizu.
Sure.
Neia, you're way too slow.
I'll take the right.
Left one is yours.
From here on out, it's a race against time.
If I slip up, just ignore me and keep going.
The rescue mission is more important than...
Um...
Wait here.
I've got a trick that I can use.
All clear.
Are you ready to go?
I can only use that full stealth ability once a day, so let's be careful.
Right, I understand.
Probably a guard.
Let's take it down immediately.
I'm ready.
Who the hell are you?
We can't get past, what should we do?
Our only option is to go on the offensive at full speed.
If we wait around, more guards will come.
So let's charge straight in.
Right.
How do humans make it to this tower in the first place?
Hehehehehehahaha!
I'm afraid projectiles don't work on me.
No one can be invincible to every kind of ranged attack.
No one on this guy's level, at least.
It's some kind of trick.
Yeah?
Try me!
You'll see!
Step away.
Look at that!
Just like I said!
Your arrows won't work on me, you dumb human!
Now die!
Merde!
Come on, you little brat!
Give it up already!
Why are you aiming for her?
You're attacking her even though her arrows are useless against you.
It doesn't make sense.
She's in the way and I hate her face!
I bet she can hurt you.
You must have a limit.
Now, Neia!
I got it!
I'll try!
Hey!
Seven times.
That's the limit.
He can resist ranged attacks like he said, but only seven times.
Is that seven in a day?
Seven in an hour?
Not sure.
Doesn't matter much either way.
You're dead now.
We'll finish you.
The hell you will!
Fuck!
He's gone around behind you.
Neia, duck!
Let's change it up.
Full burst mode.
That was really something.
Are you okay, Neia?
I'm fine.
One of my arms hurts though, so it's hard to shoot my bow.
Do you have a healing potion on you?
No, I don't.
But we just have to rescue the hostage now, so I should be all right.
Then let's go.
One of the items that his majesty gave me casts a healing spell,
but I only have enough magic power to use it once.
My arm hurts, but I'd better save it in case of an emergency.
We're here.
Ready.
It's empty.
Don't shoot him!
You had the right room after all.
This is the prince.
This thing?
Hello there.
So, uh, you can speak, can't you, prince?
Of course.
But who are you?
I assume you ladies weren't sent here to be part of my meal.
No, we're not.
Actually, we're here to set you free on behalf of another Zern.
One of my eggmates?
Uh, I just know her name is Bebebe.
Bebebe, you say?
Well, I appreciate the sentiment, but if I leave this place,
I will surely invoke Lord Jaldabaoth's wrath.
That will put my people, and most importantly, our king in terrible danger.
I don't know all the details, but it seems that your king was killed,
which is why the Zern went to rescue you at any cost.
My father?
It can't be.
The city will be liberated soon.
The Zern made an alliance with our human army.
When they hear that you're safe, they'll make their move and attack.
Very well.
I know you are heroes who have risked your lives to save me,
but I'm afraid I must ask a shameless request.
As a safety precaution, will you please act as if
you are taking me from this place against my will?
You're trying to protect your people, aren't you?
What a fine prince.
If that's the case, consider us your kidnappers.
I am grateful.
This isn't uncomfortable, is it?
I'm fine here on your shoulder, but you smell so nice that it wets my appetite a bit.
Do the Zern eat human flesh?
No, we eat bodily fluids, from the living or dead.
Don't munch on her or I'll get real mad.
Do you really think I'm voracious enough to eat my own savior during our escape?
I hope not.
Let's go.
I sense multiple people in this room.
I'll be ready.
Don't know who they are, but they're Zerns.
Is that good?
Prince, you're safe!
It's Bebebe!
I've been told that my father has passed.
But what do you plan to do?
If we run away, it will only set us on the path to destruction.
I worry too.
It's frightening.
But we cannot stay with Jaldabaoth when
he only sees us as slaves and livestock.
Even if he conquers this land, we will not find peace
judging by how he has mistreated dear Bubebe already.
Get here a bit faster next time.
Not Bubebe!
Also, as we feared, one of Jaldabaoth's demon
aids is on site here at the castle.
It's the one with two heads.
A circlet, I see.
It's a kind of demon that wears the heads of two magic casters.
Then it uses their spells.
This is a good chance.
We should kill it.
I agree.
Our future depends on your strength.
If we've come this far, then we must go all the way.
Your Highness.
No guards.
It's all alone.
Good, then.
This will be our best chance to slay it.
Let's go.
Hm.
A human?
Yin Five Elements, Grand Fireball!
Yang Five Elements, Grand Fireball!
As I thought.
Is that the Xehan Prince wrapped around that human's back?
Then I assume you're not here to offer them as a new prisoner.
A betrayal.
How interesting.
Oh no, it's her.
High Priestess, Callert Custodio.
I didn't expect this from you, Zans.
I thought we were getting along so well.
Does this mean you don't care what happens to your king?
We know that you killed him!
You can't control us with your threats anymore!
He's dead.
I hadn't heard that yet.
Oh well, it doesn't matter.
You probably killed him because he got too full of himself.
And now you'll suffer the exact same fate.
How dare you!
I know you traitors can't defeat me on your own.
Was that human supposed to be your trump card?
You'll find out!
This discussion is over.
Come forth, Shadow Demons!
Kill all the female Zans, but spare the prince.
You're going back to your room, boy.
Human, there's no chance of winning by siding with the Zans.
Do you have any friends or loved ones who have been captured?
Join me and I'll see that their lives are spared.
You mean that?
You've come this far and now you betray us?
Silence!
You're not part of this conversation, worm.
Tell me who you'd like to protect, human.
Whose lives would you like to save?
It's all in your hands.
What?
But you're...
No time to explain.
Yin 5 Elements, Lightning Claw!
Yang 5 Elements, Lightning Claw!
Little pest.
Shockwave!
Yin 5 Elements, Lightning Claw!
Yang 5 Elements, Lightning Claw!
Open wounds!
That looks bad.
Heavy, recover!
I see.
Shockwave!
Tell me you're all right!
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Tch, you're wearing some sturdy armor.
Fine, the next one will kill you.
No, I'll protect Neia with my life.
What?
And did you notice the bow she's using?
It's a masterpiece loaned to her by Lord Ainz.
What?
From the Sorcerer King?
That's right, made with Rune technology.
Shizu, don't reveal all our secrets!
It can't be.
You mean the secret weapon-making technique
that was thought to have been lost to time?
A weapon like that is so valuable.
It might even kill a great demon like me!
I don't know what's going on here.
A Rune weapon!
I never thought I would see the day!
What are Runes?
It doesn't matter!
It's just a nice bow!
Runes, though!
Shut up!
Well, all right then.
Blindness.
I can't see!
It's fine, just shoot.
Right!
Well done!
Huh?
I hit it?
Let's keep on the offensive.
Your Highness, we did it!
We're free!
Can you see now?
Uh-huh, all better now.
That's good to hear.
I can't believe we pulled that off.
Splendid work, my friends.
Now, everyone, eat Grandmother's corpse with the utmost of care.
Eat it?
Wait, was it someone you knew?
She was queen of a demi-human tribe called the Pandax.
She was also my childhood crush.
I assume you'll eat the human head before we depart?
Uh, no, that's not what we humans do when people die.
But I think we should take it home.
Very well.
Hey, Neia, our mission's complete.
I think we'd better get out of here.
All right, let's go.
Cut them all down!
Don't leave one demi-human alive!
Other than the Zans, that is!
I know, I know!
This is it!
This is our chance to stand up for justice with our own two hands!
Humans, I have returned!
Ah, I see you've chosen a fine place to die!
Seems that you've done as you please while my injuries were healing.
But all of your fun will come to an end now.
None shall escape my flames of wrath!
Wrath and suffer till naught but ash remains!
Retreat from here!
I'll fight!
You can't!
That's madness!
You should run for your life!
I can't win.
You're correct on that account.
But that's fine!
So long as I can protect others, I know what I am doing is just!
And justice is something worth dying for!
Very well, then.
Let's go!
Look, Neia.
See?
It can't be!
Those are demi-human reinforcements!
I have to notify the troops!
Hurry up!
Retreat now!
Demi-human troops are coming from the east!
They have reinforcements!
Oh no!
Spread the word before we get trapped in here!
That cursed demon!
How many pawns does he have to throw at us?
This is bad!
We can't let him get away!
They must have gathered all the remaining
demi-humans from Abelion Hills!
You should escape while you still can!
What about you?
I'm not leaving!
In the last battle, I wanted to stay by his majesty's side,
but I couldn't because I was too weak!
But as someone who served the Sorcerer King,
I can't allow it to end that way!
My weakness is a sin that I must atone for!
He protected all of these people's lives.
I have to help them escape, no matter what it takes!
Listen, Shizu.
I'll have to entrust my mission to you now.
Find his majesty in my stead.
That shouldn't be hard.
And I don't need to run away, either.
Hold on, what are you saying?
Look there!
The Sorcerer Kingdom!
That's their flag!
His majesty has returned!
He's alright!
What a coincidence meeting you here, Miss Baraja.
Did you think I was dead, perhaps?
Of course not!
I'm just glad to see you!
I've never lost faith!
Shizu said you were fine and I believed her since
we're such good friends, but I'm just so overwhelmed!
Heh, I see.
I'm happy to hear that.
But wait, you're friends?
Please don't cry.
Hmm, I see you and Shizu have grown quite close, Miss Baraja.
What a pleasant surprise.
It's all thanks to your wisdom!
You left me with a great partner!
We bonded through our love for you!
Seems you did well in my absence.
Anything else you'd like to report?
Hmm, Shizu?
Neia is awesome.
She has a unique face.
Huh?
What does that mean?
Oh wait, I'll save all of my questions until the battle is over.
But one thing.
Are you angry that we took so long to go search for you?
If so, I will take full responsibility!
Why, the thought never crossed my mind.
Everything has worked out well enough,
so I have no reason to be angry with anyone.
Your majesty...
Rather, I apologize for making you wait.
After I was defeated by Jaldabaoth, I fell into the Abyllion Hills.
It took a bit of work on my part, but the entire area
is now under the rule of the Sorcerer Kingdom.
In other words, all of the forces here belong to me!
Now, I do believe I have a bit of revenge
to take on our nemesis, Jaldabaoth.
Hey, isn't that the Sorcerer King?
He's alive after all!
His majesty's here!
The Sorcerer King!
I can't help but notice that they're calling my name.
Of course, they're celebrating the return of their hero after all.
These people owe their lives to you.
Is that really how they feel?
The humans are thanking me?
That's right!
They love you!
Courtesy of your influence, no doubt.
It seems you've grown stronger in my absence, Miss Baraja.
Thank you, your majesty!
I'm so honored that you think so!
Listen well!
Last time, I was taken by surprise.
I was outnumbered and had consumed much of my magic power.
But tonight, the circumstances are different.
There is no one who can defeat me at full strength!
Wait here, and I shall return victorious!
Fight well, your majesty!
For justice!
Indeed!
I've kept you waiting.
I failed to kill you last time.
Not today.
He won.
And you were right!
I told you so, trainee.
Glory to his majesty!
Praise the Sorcerer King!
And that is how his majesty, the Sorcerer King, defeated Jaldabaoth.
After Kalinsha, the Liberation Army pushed forward and retook the city of Prahrt.
Then, at long last, our kingdom's capital, Hoburns, was liberated as well.
His majesty, the Sorcerer King, is without equal.
He fought to bring us peace for the people of this land and demihumans too.
Demihumans don't deserve peace!
Of course, I think it's fair for you to feel that way.
They killed many people.
We can't just forget.
And yet, like us, plenty of demihumans were also victims of Jaldabaoth.
His majesty dealt with them, but he did so with kindness.
He delivered them from our kingdom and let them live safely under his flag.
Thus, we are protected too, and peace is preserved for all.
Now, I ask, have you ever heard of a king
who ventures out alone and puts his life on the line
for another kingdom just because its people are suffering?
Have you ever heard of a king who shows
kindness to all no matter their race?
Oh, uh, actually, when you put it that way, no.
And I agree!
It's just as you say!
There should be no borders when it comes to kindness,
no borders when it comes to bravery.
His majesty taught me this.
He showed me a new way to look at the world.
And that's why there's none other like him,
why he is the one and only King of Justice.
For what could be more just than wielding
strength in the name of kindness?
That is why this land and all of its people,
why all people in the world must seek peace
beneath the great wings of the Sorcerer King!
Another fine speech.
You're spreading the good word.
Well, my job is easy when his majesty has accomplished so much.
I don't deserve credit.
There's a matter I'd like to discuss with you.
Huh?
His majesty's followers have continued to grow.
We're now 50,000 strong.
Wow!
That's so uplifting to hear!
Bit by bit, people are starting to understand his majesty's greatness.
Although, that is only natural.
He saved our kingdom from complete destruction after all.
Getting back to the matter I mentioned earlier,
since our organization has grown so much,
the supporters would like to have some sort of symbol of their faith.
Oh, I see.
I must admit I hadn't thought of that.
Can I leave the matter to you?
It would be my pleasure.
I'll tell his majesty.
I'm sure he'll be as happy as we are.
Are you certain, your majesty?
Yes.
That equipment is my gift to you for all your hard work.
You've made good use of it already, after all.
Now, I shall return to the Sorcerer Kingdom.
My business here has concluded.
There's nothing more I can say.
Though I'm still sad you can't get a proper farewell.
Since you saved us, you deserve to be seen off like a hero.
I assure you that's no concern.
In fact, I specifically asked Prince Kaspar not to make a big affair of this.
And yet...
You're their savior.
They wanted to express their thanks.
Well, no need to linger.
Shizu, do you have anything you'd like to say to Miss Baraja?
See you.
All right.
I know your kingdom still has many challenges left to overcome.
However, I'm confident that you have the strength to succeed.
Let us meet again someday.
Sure.
I do have one last question.
Well, it's just...
If you don't mind, would it be all right if I call you Lord Ainz?
Yes.
If that would please you, I will allow it.
Thank you very much!
And Shizu, come back soon!
Farewell, our hero!
His Majesty, the Sorcerer King!
Hooray!
Lord Ainz, your kindness changed my life.
From now on, with every ounce of my power,
I'll spread your justice through the whole kingdom!
Despite the fact that my leadership steered us through the war,
I'm sure plenty of nobles will be quite unhappy once I become Sacred King.
Especially those in the Southern Territory,
who are far away from most of the death and violence.
As time goes on, discontent will grow,
sparking a great rift between the North and South.
Then, inevitably, the Sacred Kingdom will be split in two.
You honor me with your presence, my lord.
How may I serve you?
Just checking in, since I was already here to seize some treasure.
Have you encountered any problems thus far?
Not at all, my lord.
Everything has been proceeding exactly according to your plans.
Splendid.
Then on to the next phase.
Let us further aggravate the relationship between the North and the South.
Till we incite a civil war.
Searching for hope, or searching for asylum,
the people of this land will naturally turn to Lord Ainz.
Then, willfully, they shall give themselves fully to the Sorcerer Kingdom.
I do have one question.
Is it safe to let Neia Baraja continue with what she's doing?
Even if she spreads support for His Majesty,
I fear her popularity may outweigh the Sacred Kings in time.
Leave her be.
Lord Ainz's actions may seem inscrutable at first,
but that is only because his true genius is beyond our ken.
He has prepared a splendid pawn!
I see that now, that the pieces have fallen so neatly into place!
This is a land mired in religion, reliant on their sacred king.
And yet Lord Ainz has effortlessly forged the perfect loyal mouthpiece.
One that will expedite my plan by years.
To that end, he even staged his own death,
fooling the whole Sacred Kingdom.
His genius is terrifying.
Even amongst the Supreme Beings, he stands atop the highest peak!
Lord Ainz, I shall not rest till this whole world is in your grasp.
Now, any other questions before I'm on my way?
Yes.
Remedios Custodio.
She's no longer of any use to us.
Would it not be safer just to kill her before she causes more trouble?
Well, I wouldn't say she's completely useless.
For now, she'll serve as a fine target for the discontent of the nobles.
We'll dispose of her once both sides
have thoroughly turned against one another.
Very well, my lord.
Good then.
I'll leave you to it.
Enjoy your happiness while you can, my dear subjects.
You may find it is quite fleeting.